

OBJECTIVE

To be an active employee who contributes to the Mission, Vision, and Values of the company, and to interact, on a professional level with other employees. To give excellent performance, and to translate my experience, knowledge, skills and abilities into value.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: March 4,1996

Gender: Male

Civil Status: Single

Age: 26

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, JavaScript

C++, VB, Java

Graphic Design

Web Design

Adobe PS, AI

PC Troubleshooting

UI/UX

Analytical Thinking

Communication Skills

CONTACT

B: https://www.behance.net/matthew-calabia

F: https://www.facebook.com/Mat1017/

E: calabiamatthew@live.com

P: +63 915 778 7022

MATTHEW CALABIA

EDUCATION

2012 - Computer Programming

St. Benilde College of Science and Technology

· Best Thesis

· Best Business Proposal

2014 Computer Hardware and Servicing Training

Canossa College

• Tesda Computer Hardware Servicing NC II Exam Passer

2016 - 2020 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Laguna State Polytechnic University - San Pablo City

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Graphic Artist

Jan 2022 - present

Fraud Analyst (BPO)

September 2019 - January 2020

The Results Companies (Target-OVT) (OJT)

Pasig City, Philippines

- · Top 1 Team Member
- · Best QA Pick

Web Developer

May 2019 - June 2020

Laguna State Polytechnic University - CCS (OJT)

San Pablo City, Laguna

Computer Technician / Encoder

January 2014 - March 2014

Office of Social Welfare and Development (OJT)

San Pablo City, Laguna

Sales Utility Clerk

November 2014 - April 2015

Signature Lines Inc. Levi Strauss

San Pablo City, Laguna

REFERENCES

Mr. Ronnel A. Dela Cruz

Associate Dean, CCS

Laguna State Polytechnic University - SPC 049 562-7319